I'm 99 % sure the Death
Gun story's a hoax.
Probably someone trolling.
You can't kill someone in the real
world from the virtual anymore.
I know that's impossible.
But there's still that 1
% chance it could be true.
That's why I'm here.
Link start!
it's a lot different than halo go figure
killing people's the point
in here all right then
Uh-huh.
I'm going to give you my hand I've had
my
I've had a feeling that I didn't know
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
creepy that showdown
That's the beginning of the song It
will change the sound The only way
I wish I looked a little more soldier-ish.
Holy bazongas, that's the
F-1300 model, isn't it?
That avatar's so rare, I've
only heard about them till now.
I want it.
I'll give you two mega
credits for your account.
Come on, lady, what do you say?
Lady?
I hate to break it to you,
Guy, but I'm a guy, too.
Holy crap!
Then that means you got the M9000 model.
I'll give you four.
No, five for it. Sell it to me.
Come on, sell it to me.
Sorry, but this isn't a default avatar.
It's a converted one.
I can't exchange it for cash.
Aw, that sucks.
Yeah, well, later.
Hey, if you ever change your
mind, give me the first bit!
If I want to get Death Gun's attention,
I have to make a name for myself first.
Are you looking for some action?
Are you too good for me?
I'm totally lost.
Some shortcut this turned out to be.
Uh, excuse me, can you tell me where...
Uh-oh, she thinks I'm hitting on her.
Yeah, what?
Your first time in the game, huh?
I, um...
Oh my god, she thinks I'm a girl too.
Where do you want to go?
Uh, I, uh...
Yes, it's my first time.
I'm looking for a place
to buy a cheap gun.
Oh, and I also need to find out
where the governor's office is.
Oh, sure.
I can show you.
It's not cool, but I'll let her keep
thinking I'm a girl for a while.
By the way, why do you want to
go to the Governor's office?
Uh, I wanted to sign myself up for
an event called Bullet of Bullets.
B .O .B.?
Okay, but you just started
playing today, right? Yes.
Yeah, I don't know.
Your stats may not be
high enough for that.
Oh, well, I converted, so all my skills
have been transferred from another game.
If you say so.
So anyway, you picked a
heck of a game to play.
It's all grimy and stinks of oil.
Well, I've only played
fantasy games up to now.
They're fun, but I thought
I'd try a cyber game for once.
I was also interested in seeing
what gun battles were like.
Really?
It takes guts to want
to start with B .O .B.
right off the bat like that.
Let's hook you up with a gun, then.
I know this great market.
It's down here.
Okay.
Wow, this place looks
like it has everything.
Yeah, well,
the two types of weapons
that are mostly used
in GGO are optical guns
and live ammo guns. Huh.
An optical gun's lighter and more
accurate, but it has its drawbacks.
If your opponent equips their defense
shield, it only does half the damage.
For a one-on-one tourney like B .O .B.,
a live ammo gun's the best bet. Oh, okay.
All right.
Let's start with your stats.
Highest one first.
Um, I guess my strength is the highest.
And speed after that.
You're an S-T-R-A-G-I type, huh?
Okay, you've got two choices
for your main weapon.
Either a heavy assault rifle
or a large caliber machine gun.
Whichever one you choose, you're also going
to need a handgun for a backup weapon.
Oh, wait a sec.
You said you just
converted over, didn't you?
Do you have any credits?
Yeah, I should.
Let's see.
It says I have a thousand credits.
Everybody gets that when they start.
Oh.
Hmm.
If that's all you have, the most you can
afford's going to be a small ray gun.
And for a live ammo gun, a thousand
won't even get you a used revolver.
Listen, if you want, I could
loan you the money to buy a gun.
That's really sweet of
you, but I couldn't.
Uh, I know.
Does this game have anything in it where a
new player like me could
go earn some money?
Well, I don't recommend them, but
there are casinos and gambling games.
Like that one.
Hey, chicken! Come on!
How do you play?
You enter through that gate and go down
the alley dodging the NPC's bullets.
The idea is to get as close as you
can to him without getting shot.
If you can touch him,
you win all the cash everyone's sunk
into it since the last time it was beat.
All of it?
$300,000 change.
Now that is a heck of a lot of money.
Well, no one's beating it.
Once you get eight meters
away from the gunslinger,
he switches to this wicked
fast quick-draw mode.
By the time you see the
bullet lines, it's too late.
The bullet lines?
Look, another sucker's stepping
up to add to the jackpot.
Today's the day, man.
Yeah, you got this.
Here goes nothing.
I'm gonna blast you from here
to the moon, you varmint.
Watch me clear this
biatch and nothing flat.
Jackpot's yours.
Yeah, you know it.
Why's he doing that?
Was that the bullet line? Yup.
It's a defensive system assist.
We all have it.
Except for a sniper's first shot,
bullet prediction lines always show
up in the target's field of vision.
I'll kill you, whatever!
Run, man!
You still got this!
You loser!
Game over, hoss!
Well, that sucked.
That guy didn't have a chance.
See?
The alley's so narrow, you can't
move too far to either side,
and you're forced to charge
the gunslinger straight on.
That's about as far as anyone's gotten.
Oh, I get it.
If I wait to see the bullet
lines, it'll be too late.
Uh, hey, where are you going?
Ten Kirito says the newbie
gets it out of the gate.
Whoa, that's the cutest
target I ever seen.
Let's stick around and
watch her get pwned.
I'll kill you!
You loser!
You're kidding.
She passed the ten meter mark.
That is one fast kid.
Die, you varmint.
I'll blast you to hell.
Looks like someone's out of bullets!
Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Hey, Chicken, come on!
What the hell was that?
Who is that kid?
Oh my god, I've never
seen reflexes like that.
I mean, at the end, you dodged his
lasers from about two meters away.
At that range, the time between you seeing
the bullet lines and the shots fired,
well, that's it.
There shouldn't have been
any time between them.
Oh, uh, really?
Well, since it's a game of dodging
bullets, I just predicted the bullet lines.
You know, predict the predictions.
You...
you predicted the predictions?!
Huh?!
I'm confused about the specs
for this assault rifle. I mean,
this thing's ginormous,
so why is the caliber of the bullets it
fires smaller than a submachine gun's?
I'm confused about how
someone like you can
dodge bullets like a
ghost and not know that.
You converted from another game.
What'd you play before this one?
Nothing special.
Just one of those typical
fantasy games is all.
Hmm.
Yeah, so you said.
Well, during the B .O .B.
prelims, I'll get an idea
of what you can really do.
As for the assault rifle, you want
to know why it uses a small caliber?
Sure.
It all goes back to the M16 from the U .S.
They designed it for precision
and penetrative power,
but using a fast, small-caliber round.
You don't need to know that stuff, though.
Now that you've got 300K, you can buy
pretty much whatever gun you want.
It all comes down to what you want and
what you think will work best for you.
What does work for me?
Hey, what are these?
Oh, those are photon swords.
Photon?
It's a beam of light that's
a wave in a particle.
Photon sword's the official name,
but people call them laser blades,
beam sabers, and something else
I can't remember. Oh, cool!
You can use a sword here?
Yeah, if you want, but
nobody really uses them.
Why don't they?
Well, I mean, because.
You can't use it unless
you're close to your target.
And if you're crazy enough to get that
close, you'll get shot full of holes.
So basically, it's good as
long as you get close enough.
Yeah, I guess, but even
with your skill at dodging,
if there's a full auto gun firing, I...
Welcome, Slayer!
Thank you.
Thank you for your purchase!
Have a nice day!
Oh, well, I guess when it comes to
combat, everyone's got their own style.
The way I see it, if this place sells
something, it must be OK for battle,
even this.
Whoa.
Huh, she looks like she
knows what she's doing.
Wow, those are your fantasy game skills.
Not bad.
I know a couple of moves.
This sure is light.
Huh?
Well, looks like you're dead set
on that for your main weapon.
But you should have a submachine gun
or a handgun in your inventory, too.
It'll distract your enemy
so you can get closer.
Oh, okay.
How much do you have left?
About 150k.
Whoa, those photon thingies are expensive.
You got 150k, huh?
You still need to get protective gear or
some kind of weapon and the ammo for it.
What's cheap but good?
I'll trust your judgment with all that.
For B .O .B., a live ammo
weapon's your best bet.
If I were you, I'd go for
accuracy over stopping power.
Hmm.
Oh, you'll spend most of your
credits on it, but this one's good.
The FN-57.
What's 5.7?
The bullet caliber.
5.7 millimeters.
They're smaller than the 9mm Parabellum
bullets, but they still pack a punch.
They're similar in shape to rifle bullets,
so they've got the edge in both
precision and stopping power.
Huh.
Hey, are you even listening?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I guess I'll buy that one then.
Is that it, or do I need anything else?
Yeah, you do.
You're gonna need a holster, some
extra mags, some protective gear,
and you should also get yourself
a defense field and range time.
What's that?
You never fired a gun before,
have you? Uh-uh, never.
Let's change that.
If you buy a gun from the
shop, you can test it here.
Know how to hold it? I guess.
It's lighter than I thought.
That's cuz that models made of reinforced
plastic the recoil isn't too bad on it.
Still you should grip it with both
hands and keep your left eye open.
So right now you should be seeing a
green circle in your field of vision?
Is it supposed to be shrinking
and expanding like that?
Yep.
It's called the bullet circle,
your offensive assist system.
Your bullets will hit the target
at random inside the circle.
How do I boost my accuracy?
I guess the easiest way is to get
closer to your target. What else?
Try to stay calm.
The faster your heart beats,
the more the circle expands.
This is harder than I thought.
No way! I missed?
What'd you expect?
It's your first time!
Thank you for going
out of your way for me.
I really appreciate it. Mama.
I was happy to help.
There aren't many girl players here.
I wasn't doing anything, so it was a good
way to kill some time before the prelims.
Wait, you're going to compete in B .O .B.
too? Uh-huh.
I was on my way to sign up before...
Oh, my God!
They're closing soon. Really?
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault we're late.
No, it's mine for not
keeping track of the time.
Whatever, let's hurry.
We're never gonna make it.
Can't we just teleport over there?
I wish.
That only happens when you respawn
at a revival point after you die.
And we can't suicide ourselves to
get there either, because in town,
our HP never goes down.
The governor's office is at
least three kilometers away.
It's gonna take us five minutes to sign
up, so we have to get there in three.
Don't close.
Don't close till we get there.
That's it.
Here we go.
Better hang on!
Wait a sec!
These are supposed to be
ridiculously hard to drive!
I don't know anyone who can
handle them, so how come you can?
Oh, well, I used to play a lot
of racing games back in the day.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine!
This is great!
Go on! Punch it!
The faster, the better!
Okay!
Let's go.
It's not one thing.
I'm stronger, stronger.
I'm going to ask you to go to the dark.
Like a lonely star,
I'm deep.
Next time, Guns and Swords.
Thank you.